RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 1990-1995, 1997-012
  - 1993
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks; Commerce; Education (Box 131)
    - Unfinished Business - Children, Commerce and Exportation; Education (Box 132)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 133)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 134)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 135)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 136)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 137)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 138)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 139)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 140)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 141)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 142)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 143)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 144)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 145)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations (Box 146)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 147)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 148)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 149)
  - 1994
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 150)
    - Resolutions (Box 150)
    - Appointments (Box 150)
    - Resolutions (Box 151)
    - Public Acts, 1-33 (Box 151)
    - Public Acts, 34-68 (Box 152)
    - Public Acts, 69-87 (Box 153)
    - Public Acts, 88-110 (Box 154)
    - Public Acts, 111-122 (Box 155)
    - Public Acts, 122 (Box 156)
    - Public Acts, 123-140 (Box 157)
    - Public Acts, 141-159 (Box 158)
    - Public Acts, 160-174 (Box 159)
    - Public Acts, 175-186 (Box 160)
    - Public Acts, 187-201 (Box 161)
    - Public Acts, 202-219 (Box 162)
    - Public Acts, 220-235 (Box 163)
    - Special Acts, 1-2 (Box 164)
    - Special Acts, 3-16 (Box 165)
    - Special Session, May - Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 165)
    - Special Session, May - Public Acts, 3-6 (Box 166)
    - Special Session, May 25 - Resolutions; Public Act; Special Act (Box 166)
    - Reconvened Session, June 20 - Resolutions (Box 167)
    - Special Session, July - Resolutions; Public Acts (Box 167)
    - Special Session, July 13 - Resolutions; Public Acts (Box 167)
    - Special Session, October 12 - Resolutions; Appointments, Public Act (Box 167)
    - Special Session, November - Resolutions; Public Acts; Special Act (Box 167)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 168)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 169)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 170)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks; Children; Commerce (Box 171)
    - Unfinished Business - Commerce; Education; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 172)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 173)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 174)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 175)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 176)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 177)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 178)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 179)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 180)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 181)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 182)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 183)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 184)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; No Committee Name; Special Session, May; Special Session, July 13 (Box 185)
  - 1995
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 186)
    - Appointments (Box 186)
    - Appointments (Box 187)
    - Public Acts, 1-19 (Box 187)
    - Public Acts, 20-54 (Box 188)
    - Public Acts, 55-79 (Box 189)
    - Public Acts, 80-117 (Box 190)
    - Public Acts, 118-140 (Box 191)
    - Public Acts, 141-160 (Box 192)
    - Public Acts, 161-183 (Box 193)
    - Public Acts, 184-195 (Box 194)
    - Public Acts, 196-224 (Box 195)
    - Public Acts, 225-233 (Box 196)
    - Public Acts, 234-252 (Box 197)
    - Public Acts, 253-263 (Box 198)
    - Public Acts, 264-276 (Box 199)
    - Public Acts, 277-290 (Box 200)
    - Public Acts, 291-310 (Box 201)
    - Public Acts, 311-327 (Box 202)
    - Public Acts, 328-348 (Box 203)
    - Public Act 349 (Box 204)
    - Special Acts, 1-4 (Box 204)
    - Special Acts, 5-19 (Box 205)
    - Special Act 20 (Box 206)
    - Trailer Session - Resolutions (Box 206)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 206)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 207)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 208)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 209)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 210)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Environment (Box 211)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 212)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 213)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; Executive and Legislative Nominations; General Law (Box 214)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 215)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 216)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services (Box 217)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 218)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 219)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 220)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 221)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 222)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor (Box 223)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 224)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 225)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 226)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 227)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 228)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 229)
    - Special Session, October - Resolutions; Rejected Bill (Box 229)
- 1996, 1997-058
  - 1996
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 1)
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointments (Box 1)
    - Trailer Session (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-45 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 46-82 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 83-119 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 120-146 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 147-167 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 168-180 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 181-197 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 198-218 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 219-239 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 240-248 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 249-259 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 260-271 (Box 13)
    - Special Acts, 1-17 (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology; Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, General Law, Government Administration and Elections (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Labor and Public Employees (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health; Public Safety (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; transportation; No Committee Name (Box 31)
- 1997, 1998-033
  - 1997
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointments (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-46 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 47-87 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 88-119 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 120-147 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 148-172 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 173-193 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 194-214 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 215-235 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 236-246 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 247-258 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 259-272 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 273-293 (Box 13)
    - Public Acts, 294-310 (Box 14)
    - Public Acts, 311-322 (Box 15)
    - Special Acts, 1-20 (Box 16)
    - Special Acts, 21 (Box 17)
    - Trailer Session (Box 18)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-2; Special Act (Box 18)
    - Special Session, June 18 - Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 18)
    - Special Session, June 18 - Public Acts, 3-11 (Box 19)
    - Special Session, July 21 - Resolutions; Public Act (Box 20)
    - Special Session, October 29 - Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Environment (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, General Law (Box 32)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 33)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 34)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 35)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 36)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate (Box 37)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 38)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 39)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 40)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 41)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 42)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 43)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 44)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, No Committee Name; Special Session, Jun 18 (Box 46)
- 1998, 1999-171
  - 1998
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointments (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-27 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 28 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 29-69 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 70-103 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 104-124 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 125-142 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 143-164 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 165-183 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 184-203 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 204-219 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 220-239 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 240-248 (Box 13)
    - Public Acts, 249-255 (Box 14)
    - Public Acts, 256-264 (Box 15)
    - Special Acts, 1-9 (Box 15)
    - Trailer Session - Resolutions (Box 16)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions, Public Act (Box 16)
    - Special Session, December - Resolutions, Public Act (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Childcare; Commerce; Education (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Environment (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue, Bonding, General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety; Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 29)
- 1999-2000, 2005-016
  - 1999
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-46 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts-47-94 (Box 3)
    - Public acts, 95-133 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 134-164 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 165-180 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 181-195 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 196-222 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 223-2441 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 242-261 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 262-284 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 285-290 (Box 12)
    - Special Acts, 1-17 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions (Box 13)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology; Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Heath (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 32)
  - 2000
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 33)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 33)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 33)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 33)
    - Public Acts, 1-14 (Box 33)
    - Public Acts, 15-44 (Box 34)
    - Public Acts, 45-90 (Box 35)
    - Public Acts, 91-122 (Box 36)
    - Public Acts, 123-149 (Box 37)
    - Public Acts, 150-173 (Box 38)
    - Public Acts, 174-192 (Box 39)
    - Public Acts, 193-220 (Box 40)
    - Public Acts, 221-231 (Box 41)
    - Special Acts, 1-13 (Box 41)
    - Special Session, May - Resolutions (Box 41)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions (Box 41)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 41)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 42)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 43)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 44)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Executive and Legislative Nominations; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 46)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 47)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 48)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 49)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Judiciary (Box 50)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 51)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 52)
    - Unfinished Business - Program Review and Investigations; Public Health (Box 53)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 54)
- 2001, 2006-026
  - 2001
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Trailer (Veto) Session Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-47 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 48-78 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 79-107 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 108-131 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 132-140 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 141-162 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 163-180 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 181-195 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 196-211 (Box 10)
    - Special Acts, 1-12 (Box 11)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions (Box 11)
    - Special Session, November 15 - Resolutions (Box 11)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-9 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, June - Special Acts, 1-2 (Box 13)
    - Special Session, November 15 - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 13)
    - Special Session, November 15 - Special Act 1 (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Commerce; Education (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - General Administration and Elections (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 32)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 33)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 34)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 35)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Heath (Box 36)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 37)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 38)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Workforce Development; No Committee Name; Draft list of Unfinished Business Bills and Resolutions (Box 39)
- 2002-2004, 2007-008
  - 2002
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-38 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 39-69 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 70-73 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 74-90 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 91-111 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 112-131 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 132-143 (Box 8)
    - Special Acts, 1-12 (Box 8)
    - Special Acts, 13-16 (Box 9)
    - Special Session, May 9 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 9)
    - Special Session, May 9 - Public Acts, 1-7 (Box 9)
    - Special Session, May 9 - Special Ac 1 (Box 9)
    - Special Session, December 18 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 9)
    - Special Session, January 6, 2003 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 9)
    - Special Session, January 6, 2003 - Public Act 1 (Box 9)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 10)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 11)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 12)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing; Human Services (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Heath (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Committee Transmittal Letters for Unfinished Business and Resolutions; Draft List of Unfinished Business Bills and Resolutions; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 27)
  - 2003
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 28)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 28)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 28)
    - Public Acts, 1-18 (Box 29)
    - Public Acts, 19-57 (Box 30)
    - Public Acts, 58-84 (Box 31)
    - Public Acts, 85-120 (Box 32)
    - Public Acts, 121-145 (Box 33)
    - Public Acts, 146-168 (Box 34)
    - Public Acts, 169-185 (Box 35)
    - Public Acts, 186-203 (Box 36)
    - Public Acts, 204-224 (Box 37)
    - Public Acts, 225-241 (Box 38)
    - Public Acts, 242-258 (Box 39)
    - Public Acts, 259-269 (Box 40)
    - Public Acts, 270-279 (Box 41)
    - Special Acts, 1-19 (Box 42)
    - Special Session, June 16 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 43)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 43)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Public Acts, 1-3 (Box 43)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 44)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Public Acts, 4-6 (Box 44)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Special Act 1 (Box 44)
    - Special Session, June 30 - Unfinished Business (Box 44)
    - Special Session, July 1 - No Documents (Box 44)
    - Special Session, September 8 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 45)
    - Special Session, September 8 - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 45)
    - Special Session, September 8 - Special Act, 1-2 (Box 45)
    - Special Session, January 2004 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 45)
    - Special Session, January 26, 2004 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 46)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 47)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 48)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 49)
    - Unfinished Business - Banking; Children; Commerce; Education (Box 50)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology; Environment (Box 51)